# J HAN AYE



 $\bigvee$ 

jaeehan@gmail.com



jaeehan.github.io



https://www.linkedin.com/in/jaeehan



Vancouver, B.C.

## PROFILE

Bachelors of Technology student with strong analytical, communication, organizational, and teamwork skills through 5+ years of research and sales experience. Great understanding of programming, data structures, algorithms, and recursive functions through courses and personal projects.

# SKILLS

### **PROGRAMMING**

- Java
- Python
- JavaScript/CSS

### **DATABASE**

MySQL

## TOOLS

# INTEGRATED DEVELOPMENT ENVIRONMENT

- IntelliJ
- PyCharm
- Eclipse
- Visual Studio

#### WORKFLOW

- Git
- Agile/Scrum
- UML
- REST API

# EDUCATION

### **BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY**

Kwantlen Polytechnic University
Dec 2022

# PYTHON BOOTCAMP FROM ZERO TO HERO BY JOSE PORTILLA

Udemy Course
Mar 2021

# PROJECT EXPERIENCE

### **MAZE PATH FINDER**

Sep 2022 - Oct 2022

- Generate the shortest route in a given maze by using the breadthfirst-search algorithm
- Technologies: Python, PyCharm IDE

### **REACT PERSONAL WEBSITE**

May 2021 - Jul 2021

- Deployed and hosted the React application through GitHub pages
- Designed the website to maximize functionality and maintain simplicity
- Technologies: React, CSS, JavaScript, Visual Studio Code, GitHub

### **SNAKE GAME**

Jan 2021 - Apr 2021

- · Implemented graphical interfaces using Swing and AWT
- Brainstormed game concepts and design elements
- Technologies: Java, IntelliJ IDE

### **GUESS THE WORD GAME**

Aug 2020 - Sep 2020

- Gained better understanding of game development through testing and fixing errors
- Technologies: Python, Pycharm IDE

## EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

### SALES ASSOCIATE, EYESTAR OPTICAL

Nov 2019 - Apr 2021

- Supported company mission while providing a positive store culture
- Educated customers about suitable prescription lenses options

### SALES ASSOCIATE, ZERO TIME ACCESSORIES

Apr 2014 - Dec 2016

- · Helped build company website using Wix
- Designed UI/UX interface and developed webpages